quiz_data_1 = [
    {
        "question": "What does STOP stand for?",
        "choices": ["Stop, Talk, Observe, Prevent", "Support, Treat, Observe, Prevent", "Save, Treat, Observe, Prevent", "Stop, Talk, Observe, Place"],
        "answer": "Stop, Talk, Observe, Prevent"
    },
    {
        "question": "When would it be appropriate to commence CPR?",
        "choices": ["As soon as possible", "If Patient is Not Breathing", "Never. Let Professionals handle CPR", "If the patient is unconscious"],
        "answer": "If Patient is Not Breathing"
    },
    {
        "question": "PER is used for what type of injury?",
        "choices": ["Concussions", "Fractures", "Muscle Tears", "Bleeding"],
        "answer": "Bleeding"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is not a cause of Shock?",
        "choices": ["Loss of Blood", "Blisters", "Loss of Fluids", "Heart Attack"],
        "answer": "Blisters"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the management for neck and spinal injuries?",
        "choices": ["Massage Therapy", "Ice Pack Application", "Immobilisation and Transportation to Medical Facility", "Dynamic Stretching"],
        "answer": "Immobilisation and Transportation to Medical Facility"
    },
    {
        "question": "What movement method would be used for an unconscious patient?",
        "choices": ["Drag Method", "Four Handed Seat Method", "Chair Lift Method", "Human Crutch"],
        "answer": "Drag Method"
    },
    {
        "question": "When would there need to medical referral?",
        "choices": ["CPR was required", "Open Wound", "Patient is in Mental Distress", "Medication was Used"],
        "answer": "CPR was required"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the effect of the recovery position on a patient?",
        "choices": ["Relaxes Spine and Vertebrae", "Encourages Healthy Blood Flow", "Keeps Airways Clear and Open", "Stimulates Nervous Response"],
        "answer": "Keeps Airways Clear and Open"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whose safety should be ensured first?",
        "choices": ["The Casualty", "Bystanders", "Yourself", "Whoever is at Most Risk"],
        "answer": "Yourself"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the correct order of the basic life action plan",
        "choices": ["Response, Send for help, Danger, Breathing, Airways, Defibrillation, Compression", "Danger, Breathing, Response, Airways, Compression, Defibrillation, Send for help", "Danger, Response, Send for help, Airways, Breathing, Compression, Defibrillation", "Send for help, Danger, Response, Breathing, Airways, Compression, Defibrillation"],
        "answer": "Danger, Response, Send for help, Airways, Breathing, Compression, Defibrillation"
    }
    # Add more questions here
]